Austin Rowe Web Developer

(205)-807-4715

amrowe2018@gmail.com

https://github.com/Austin-Rowe

Skills

- React
- Redux
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Node/Express
- PostgreSQL
- AWS

Notable Experience

Iris Global Harvest School of Missions

The Harvest School is a 3 month school in Pemba, Mozambique. It includes an optional extended outreach that I went on into the Middle East for 2 weeks. This was an incredible experience that gave me a deep passion for missions and seeing the lost reached.

Projects

RugZilla

Ecommerce site created with React, Redux, Node, Express, Paypal, and AWS. You can check it out here.

hireAustinRowe.com

Portfolio site created with React.

Chrome Extension

Chrome extension created using vanilla JS, DOM manipulation, and OOJ. Can be viewed here.

Work History

United Textiles Retail Associate

December 2015 - Present

Whole Foods Market Cashier

May 2015 - October 2015

Zaxby's Cook/Cashier

August 2014 - May 2015

Chick-fil-A Cashier

June 2012 - August 2014

Education

Node, SQL, & PostgreSQL - Mastering Backend Web Development

May 2018

SQL & PostgreSQL for Beginners

April 2018

Team TreeHouse Front-End Developer Track

January 2018 - March 2018

Hoover High School

Graduated May 2015